谁给我解释一下
Okay, help me out here.
一位考古学教授怎么会把鞭子玩得那么溜
How does an archeology professor get that good with a whip?
估计是在成人书店学的吧[暗指SM]
Maybe he took a class at the adult bookstore.
反正我是这么学的
That's how I learned.
真不敢相信你居然没看过《法柜奇兵》
I can't believe you've never seen  Raiders of the Lost Ark.
经典动作大片《夺宝奇兵》系列的第一部
我也不敢相信你居然没看过《饭·祷·爱》
And I can't believe you've never read  Eat, Pray, Love.
《美食·祈祷·恋爱》亦作《一辈子做女孩》
要是写一本
When she comes out with
《吃饭·祈祷·躲避大滚石》  我就看
Eat, Pray, Run Away From A   Giant Boulder, I'll read it.
我才不管《饭·祷·爱》对你的人生有多大影响呢
I don't care if Eat, Pray, Love changed your life,
我才不看呢
I'm not reading it.
知道吗  我也能那么转帽子
You know, I could totally rock a hat like that.
那可是著名的好莱坞服装设计师德博拉·纳杜曼的
That's the work of noted Hollywood costume designer
杰作
Deborah Nadoolman.
她还设计了
She also designed
迈克尔·杰克逊的《战栗》的MV中
the iconic red and black jacket
那件经典的红黑夹克
in Michael Jackson's Thriller video,
不过我一直没看完MV
which I've never viewed in its entirety,
因为我觉得一群僵尸
as I find zombies dancing
跳舞这么整齐实在是太假了
in choreographed synchronicity implausible.
而且  真的好吓人啊
And also, it's really scary.
麻烦哪位帮忙把谢尔顿评论音轨给关掉吧
Would someone please turn off the Sheldon commentary track?
不好意思没有开关  你就好好听着
There's no switch. Just listen and learn.
佩妮  如果你觉得这片子不错的话
Penny, if you think this is good,
你可以周五和我们一起
you should come with us Friday
在科洛尼奥电影院的大屏幕上再看一遍
to see it on the big screen at the Colonial.
位于宾州凤凰镇  是电影《斑点》的拍摄地和纪念地
我现在就在看啊
Well, I'm watching it now.
干嘛还要周五再看一遍
Why would I want to see it again on Friday?
因为周五那场的胶片
Because the print they're showing on Friday
有首次公映的21秒加长镜头哦
has an additional 21 seconds of previously unseen footage.
什么  21秒  那不就像是看一部全新的电影了吗
What? 21 seconds? That'll be like seeing a whole new movie!
没错
Exactly.
据说加长片段能解释关于潜艇的争论
They say it finally solves the submarine controversy.
莱纳德
Did-- Leonard?
我不确定哈  但是我觉得
I'm no expert, but I believe
佩妮刚才那话是在讽刺咱们
what we just heard from Penny was sarcasm.
哇  又猜对了
Oh! Good.
本月26中8了
I'm 8 for 26 this month.
嗯  我还是算了吧
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
你们几位好好享受这21秒吧
But you guys enjoy your extra 21 seconds.
要是我能让你能明白
Bet if I could make you understand
这玩意儿有多酷的话  咱俩肯定还在一起
why this is such a cool thing, we'd still be together.
嗯  没错  不  不可能了
Mm, yeah, no, we wouldn't.
对
Uh-huh.
我猜佩妮这"21秒"跟"那个"也有关系
I'm guessing 21 seconds had something to do with that, too.
生活大爆炸第四季第八集
请允许我指出
May I point out to you all
电影院的座位都是先到先得的
that the screening is "first come, first served"?
淡定  现在才5点  电影12点才开始
Relax, it's 5:00. The movie doesn't start till midnight.
但要是换种说法
Another way of saying that is
"电影12点开演  现在已经5点了"
"the movie starts at midnight, and it's already 5:00."
咱们出发吧
Let's go.
如果我们没赶上的话  我们下半辈子
You know, if we miss it, we'll have the fun of
就能享受谢尔顿无休止的抱怨悔恨了
listening to Sheldon whine about it for the rest of our lives.
看见没  霍华德也等不及了
See? Howard's on my side.
其实我不是那意思
Actually, I'm not.
我是用讽刺手法调戏你
I'm using sarcasm to mock you.
靠  跌到27中8了
Drat. Now I'm 8 for 27.
别担心了  谢尔顿  我们能赶上的
Don't worry, Sheldon.We'll be fine.
上次和我一起排了14小时队的
What happened to the Leonard Hofstadter
莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德怎么了
who waited in line with me for 14 hours
去看《星际迷航:复仇女神》的午夜首映那次
to see the midnight premiere of Star Trek: Nemesis?
哦  他排了14个小时的队
Oh. Well, he waited in line for 14 hours,
而你却在躺椅上睡大觉
while you napped in a lawn chair,
他在离队去尿尿的时候
he got in a fight with a Klingon
和一个克林贡人吵了起来
when he stepped out of line to pee
而你却不愿起来证明他没有插队
and you wouldn't wake up to vouch for him,
最恶劣的是  他还看了《星际迷航:复仇女神》
and worst of all, he saw Star Trek: Nemesis.
但我俩的座位如何
But how were our seats?
相当好
Excellent.
那不就结了
I rest my case.
艾米  你难道不觉得我们现在就该去排队吗
Amy, don't you agree we should leave now and get in line?
其实作为你们这个社交团体的最新成员
Actually, as the newest member of your social group,
我觉得偶尔偏向你们的朋友们一方
I believe I'll gain more acceptance by arbitrarily
更能让我融入你们
siding with your friends from time to time.
真阴险
Shrewd.
莱纳德  你说得对
Leonard, you're right.
我们就应该好好享受完美食再过去
We should enjoy our meal, arrive late,
冒着最后坐上超烂座位的风险
and risk winding up with terrible seats,
当然  前提是我们都能进得去
assuming we get in at all.
多谢了  艾米
Thank you, Amy.
看见了吧  很管用的
See? It's working.
咚咚咚
Knock-knock.
谁呀
Who's there?
橄榄[我爱你]
Olive.[I love u]
我也爱你
Olive you, too.
二位  这有点儿太俗了吧
Guys, that's really starting to get old.
咚咚咚
Knock-knock.
谁啊
Who's there?
哥有马子你干瞪眼
I have a girlfriend and you don't.
哈哈哈
Hysterical!
等等  我还不知道呢  他还没说完
Wait, now, we don't know that yet. He isn't finished.
哥有马子你干瞪眼姓什么
I have a girlfriend and you don't who?
你真的不想和我们一起去看《夺宝奇兵》吗
So. Are you sure you don't want to come with us to Raiders?
不去了  那部片子里有熔化的人脸
Oh, no. That movie has melting faces.
总是会让我想起
It reminds me too much of the time
我上次把一小瓶食肉细菌
I dropped that vial of flesh-eating bacteria
掉在恒河猴实验室的情景
into the Rhesus monkey lab.
而且佩妮和我今晚有个女生之夜
Besides, Penny and I are having a girls' night tonight.
女生之夜  什么意思
Girls' night?  What does that entail?
哦  闺蜜们聚在一起啊
Oh, you know, girls get together,
一起玩儿  分享闺房密语
hang out, share girl talk.
我也是女生
I'm a girl.
也许你也可以来  我问问佩妮吧
Oh. Well, maybe you can join us. I'll ask Penny.
没必要  佩妮跟我可亲近了
No need. Penny and I are very close.
是吗
You are?
那是  事实上  我们的生理期都同步的
Yes. In fact, our menses are synchronized.
佩妮
Penny.
伯纳黛特说你们今晚要搞女生之夜
Bernadette tells me you're planning a girls' night.
我是女生
I'm a girl.
这只是  本来想着只有我和伯纳黛特的
Oh. Um, it was -- it was just going to be me and Bernadette.
再说  你不是跟谢尔顿
Besides, I thought you were going to the movies
还有那几个男人去看电影吗
with Sheldon and the guys.
是的  但是他们又不是女生
Yes, but they're not girls.
我是女生
I'm a girl.
不  对  对  我呃懂的
Yeah, no, no, I-I-I got that.
有什么着装要求
What's the dress code?
穿你觉得舒服的衣服就行
Uh, just wear something comfortable.
好的  我得去买几件才行了
All right. I'll have to go shopping.
咚咚咚
Knock-knock.
谁呀
Who is there?
-休  -休什么
- Hugh.  - Hugh who?
休·大家都得听我的
Hugh people need to listen to me.
该去排队看电影了
It's time to get in line for the movie.
你们这种敲门游戏就应该这么玩的
And that's how you tell a knock-knock joke.
一般情况下  我会说"告诉过你们啦"
Under normal circumstances I'd say, "I told you so".
但是既然我已经无数次
But as I have told you so
愤怒地告诉过你们了
with such vehemence and frequency already,
所以现在这句话已经没有意义了
the phrase has lost all meaning.
因此  我要换种说法
Therefore, I will be replacing it with the phrase:
我已经如是告知过你们了
"I informed you thusly".
啊  那我真是等不及了
Ooh. Can't wait for that to start.
我已经如是告知过你们了
I informed you thusly.
28中8了
8 for 28.
我们要是没去吃晚饭的话
This is where we could have been
现在就应该站在这儿
if we hadn't stopped for dinner.
要是库萨帕里没点甜品的话
This is where we could have been
我们现在就应该站在这儿
if Koothrappali hadn't ordered dessert.
那是我应得的老兄  我把西兰花都吃掉了
Well I earned it, dude, I ate all my broccoli.
现在我们只能站在这儿  作为人海一粟
And here's where we are. The runts in a large litter.
永远也赶不上
Unlikely to ever reach
印第安纳·琼斯的精彩视觉盛宴了
the nourishing teats of Indiana Jones.
看来幸好我们吃了晚餐
So I guess it's a good thing we stopped for dinner.
伙计们  当面对沮丧时
You know, guys, when facing disappointment,
《饭·祷·爱》教导我们
Eat, Pray, Loveteaches us --
闭嘴吧
Oh, shut up.
总而言之  长话短说
...So anyway, to make a long story short,
结果我的子宫颈异常地紧
turns out I have an unusually firm cervix.
我说艾米啊  我们说要谈女生话题的时候
You know -- Amy, when we say "girl talk",
不一定是要谈论我们的女性部位的
it doesn't just have to be about our lady parts.
真可惜  因为我有个很精彩的故事
Shame. 'Cause I have a real zinger
是关于我倾斜的子宫的
about my tilted uterus.
佩妮  你的指甲好漂亮
Penny, your nails look great.
谢谢  我是在阿罕布拉宫找到这地方的
Oh, thanks. I found this place in Alhambra.
是在一个女士地下廉价商场里
It's in a woman's basement.
虽然我觉得那只是拉皮条的幌子
I think it's a front for human trafficking,
不过他们的手艺倒真是不错
but they do a really good job.
我的一个同事的毕业论文就写的是
A colleague of mine did her graduate thesis on the fungus
消毒不当的美甲工具上滋生的霉菌
that grows on improperly sterilized manicure implements.
别说这不是女生话题
Well don't tell me that's not "girl talk".
我们今晚去哪好呢
So where should we go tonight?
酒吧  俱乐部  还是去看电影呢
A bar? A club? A movie?
或者我们也可以待在这
Or we could just stay here.
没错  继续交流感情
Yes, a continue to bond.
我预感今晚过后
I have a feeling that after tonight,
你们其中一个将成为我一辈子的好友
one of you will become my best friend forever.
或是"死党"  要是你们喜欢的话
Or "BFF," if you prefer.
我不喜欢
Which I don't.
好吧  开了单身二号吧[纯应景]
All right, time to open Bachelor Number Two.
我觉得我不应该再喝了
Gee, I don't know if I should drink more.
我还得开车回家呢  我现在的视力
I have to drive home, and I've got enough trouble
就已经看不清仪表盘了
seeing over the dashboard as it is.
没关系  你可以在我这睡
That's okay. You can just sleep here.
太棒了  睡衣派对
Oh, good, a slumber party!
我们可以变装  打耍人电话
We'll do makeovers, initiate phony phone calls,
然后穿着蕾丝睡衣玩枕头大战
and have spirited pillow fights in our frilly nighties!
天啊  艾米
Oh, gosh, Amy.
我不确定这是你所想的那种睡衣派对
I don't know if I would call this an actual slumber party.
太让人失望了
Well, that's disappointing.
我一直都想被人邀请去睡衣派对的
I've always wanted to be invited to a slumber party.
你从没参加过吗
Oh, you never were?
小的时候也没有吗
Not even when you were a kid?
有一次我做完切除扁桃体的手术以后
Well, there was the time I had my tonsils out,
跟一个越南女孩一起住在病房里
and I shared a room with a little Vietnamese girl.
结果她半夜就死了
She didn't make it through the night,
但是在那之前  都还挺好玩的
but up till then, it was kind of fun.
好吧  那我们就搞个睡衣派对吧
Okay. Well, I guess we're having a slumber party.
枕头大战
Pillow fight!
希望他们能早点放我们进去
Oh, I hope they let us in soon.
我不想总是跑到加油站去上厕所了
I'm tired of running to the gas station to use the bathroom.
加油站那家伙每次都逼我买佳得乐
The guy makes me buy a Gatorade every time.
简直是恶性循环
It's a vicious circle.
可惜你没有排队伴侣
Too bad you don't have a stadium pal like me.
什么是排队伴侣
What's a stadium pal?
这么说吧
Let me put it this way:
它能解决厕所问题
takes care of the bathroom problem,
还能给你的小腿保暖
and it keeps your calf warm.
伙计们  坏消息  我刚刚算了一下
Hey, guys, bad news. I just did a quick calculation.
根据电影院的大小和队伍的长度
Given the size of the theater and the length of this line,
我们可能没座位了
we might not get seats.
他说什么
What did he say?
干得好  拉杰
Nice going, Raj.
好不容易让他睡觉的
Just got him down for his nap.
我们有可能买不到票
We might not get seats?!
肯定有的  放心  继续睡觉吧
It's fine, it's fine.Go back to sleep.
我早知会过你们了  我早知会过你们了
Oh, I informed you thusly! I so informed you thusly.
霍华德  你来安抚他吧
Howard, you talk to him.
霍华德
Howard?
你在尿尿  对吧
You're peeing, aren't you?
瞧瞧谁来了
Hey, look who's here!
你们好啊  伙计们
Hey, buddies!
这不是《星际迷航》里的
Well, if it isn't Wil Wheaton,
加·加·宾克斯——威尔·惠顿吗
the Jar Jar Binks of the Star Trek universe.
偶们觉得你形容得真有意思[模仿加·加·宾克斯说话]
(la Ja Ja Binks)Mee-sa think that very funny!
你偶等可以排到最后面  慢慢回味
Well, you-sa can go think that at the back of the line.
不能插队  没有但是  没有椰汁
No cuts, no buts, no coconuts.
威尔·惠顿
Wil Wheaton.
我就是
Yeah.
我可是你的忠实粉丝
I'm a big fan.
粉什么  那把修整不齐的络腮胡吗
Of what? Poorly executed beards?
你有办法能让我和我的朋友进去看电影吗
Do you think you could get me and my friends into the movie?
因为我们来得有点晚了
We got here a little late.
没问题  跟我来  我带你们进去
No problem. Come on, I'll hook you up.
太棒了
Awesome.
偶们要进去看电影了  拜拜
We-sa gonna go into the movie now! Bye-bye!
现在放的是《夺宝奇兵》
This is Indiana Jones,
不是《星际迷航》
not Star Trek.
像这种伪名人根本不值得为他开后门
There should be no value to his pseudo-celebrity here!
即使是在《星际迷航》里
And even at Star Trek conventions,
如果他是来帮忙的  才放他进去呢
they only let him in if he helps set up!
淡定  谢尔顿
Calm down, Sheldon.
才不淡定呢
I will not calm down.
我们不能默许这种对公平和规矩公然侮辱的行为
This affront to justice and decency cannot go unanswered.
让·吕克·皮卡特船长曾经说过
As Captain Jean-Luc Picard once said,
"忍无可忍  无须再忍"
"The line must be drawn here!
"这就是底线  绝不后退半步"
"This far, no farther!"
你非得把他弄醒  这下爽了吧
Had to wake him up from his nap, didn't you?
你们知道我最爱霍华德什么吗
You know what I really love about Howard?
他的胸毛
His chest hair.
霍华德胸前还毛茸茸的啊
Howard has a hairy chest?
不  就一根
No, just the one.
但是真的很长
But it's really long.
好了  你看  热辣的日出红
Okay, there you go-- Sultry Sunrise Red.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我的指甲从来没有这么漂亮过
My nails have never looked so pretty before.
洗掉
Get it off.
哇  哇  好像开始
Oh, oh, uh, looks like they're getting ready
让人进场了
to let people in.
听听威尔·惠顿先生是怎么在推特上炫耀的
Listen to what Mr. Wil Wheaton is tweeting.
"坐在电影院最棒的位置上看《夺宝奇兵》
"Best seats in house for Raiders screening.
羡慕嫉妒恨吧  谢尔顿·库珀"
Suck on that, Sheldon Cooper."
你为什么要他看的推特
Why do you read his Twitter feed?
明知道那只会让自己不高兴
You know it's only going to upset you.
知己知彼  方能百战不殆   莱纳德
I believe in knowing my enemy, Leonard.
如果早几百年有推特  卡斯特上将
Had Twitter existed at the time, would not General Custer
[小巨角战役  是印第安战争的史诗]
会不去关注史汀·布尔的吗
have followed the tweets of Sitting Bull?
李将军不会关注格兰特将军的吗
Would not Lee have followed Grant?
[尤利塞斯·S·格兰特和罗伯特·E·李签订了北部弗吉尼亚李军队投降的条约]
难道间谍之间不会互相关注吗
Would not Spy have followed Spy?
我还能举更多例子  但我要先接个电话
I have more examples, but excuse me.
喂
Hello.
居然选择这种奇怪的时间来测试
Well, this seems like an odd time
我的电话通话质量  不过继续吧
to test my cell phone quality, but go on.
测试词组  好吧
Test phrases? All right.
我是个十
Im a tote.
足的傻
Ulba.
子
Twad.
连起来说吗
All together?
我是个十足的傻子
I'm a total buttwad.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
还在吗
Hello?
姐妹们  耍人的电话就该这么打
And that, girls, is how you make a phony phone call.
我不确定我有没有
I'm not sure I grasp
完全领会到笑点在哪  不过还凑合吧
the full entertainment value, but all right.
维基百科里列举睡衣派对活动的下一项是
Next on Wikipedia's list of slumber party activities:
真心话大冒险
"Truth or Dare."
好吧  你倡议的游戏  你先来
Okay, it's your game. You go first.
等下  我正在熟悉游戏规则
Hang on. I'm familiarizing myself with the rules.
看起来很通俗易懂
Seems fairly straightforward.
伯纳黛特  真心话还是大冒险
Bernadette, truth or dare?
-真心话  -听好了
- Truth. - All right.
你要把牛肉加热到什么温度
To what temperature must you heat beef
才能把引起牛海绵状脑病[即疯牛病]的
in order to kill the prion
朊病毒彻底杀死
that cses bovinespongiform encephalopathy?
这个嘛
Um...
记住  你要如实回答
Remember, you have to answer honestly.
等下  不是这样的  艾米
Wait. No, Amy, you're supposed to ask her
你要问一些私人的或者尴尬的问题
something personal or embarrassing.
好  我懂了
Oh. All right.
你的乳晕的圆周长为多少
What is the circumference of your areolas?
"用力咀嚼附赠的爆米花"
"Munching on complimentary popcorn.
嚯  嚯"
Woot, woot."
真是厚颜无耻
Oh, the gall.
我真希望他下一条推特是  "爆米花卡到气管里
I hope his next tweet is  "Popcorn lodged in trachea.
窒息致死
Choking to death.
嚯  嚯"
Woot, woot."
伙计们  真抱歉  满员了
Guys, I am sorry.We are full up.
不要
No!
我们全满了
We're full up.
我们真的很想看这场电影
We really want to see this.
你能不能通融一下
Isn't there anything you can do?
抱歉  影院防火规定不能超员
Sorry. Fire regulations.
你们应该早点来排队
Should've gotten here earlier.
这明显就是卑鄙的职员
This is nothing but ablatant abuse of power
在滥用权利
by a petty functionary.
解释下为什么威尔·惠顿和他的跟班能进去
Explain to me why Wil Wheaton and his lackeys
而我们却不能
get in and we don't.
因为我是个手里有权的小气职员  小子
'Cause I'm the petty functionary with a clipboard, bitch.
看来就这样了
I guess that's that.
回家吧
Let's go home.
我想用回那句"我早说过的"
You know what? I'm going back to "I told you so."
我早说过的
I told you so.
我们可以看其他的嘛
We can still see something.
桑德拉·布洛克的新片附近影院就有放映
Oh, the new Sandra Bullock movie is playing two blocks away.
桑德拉的片子一向有看头的
You know Sandy B. always brings it.
看  侧门
Look-- a side door.
快来  肖特·朗德
Come on, Short Round.
我看最好还是跟上他
I guess we'd bettergo after him.
肖特·朗德
Short Round?
《魔域奇兵》里跟琼斯一起的小孩
Indy's young sidekick from Temple of Doom.
《夺宝奇兵》的第二部
我知道那是谁  但干嘛叫我
Yeah, I know who itis, but why is it me?
对  应该叫个可爱的亚裔男孩
You're right. It shouldbe a cuddly Asian boy.
比如我
Like me.
让阿伯沙朗吻她下面那只眼
"And Absalom has kissed her nether eye,
还让尼古拉的屁股烫了一下
"And Nicholas is branded on the butt.
故事说完了  愿上帝保佑大家
This tale is done, and God save all the rout."
这什么玩意儿
What the hell was that?
伯纳黛特让我大冒险讲个荤段子
Bernadette dared me to tell a dirty story.
乔叟的《磨坊主的故事》是我知道的最荤的
"The Miller's Tale" by Chaucer is the dirtiest story I know.
要是14世纪的人穿袜子的话
It would have been hidden in sock drawers
就该把它塞在脏袜子抽屉里
if people in the 14th century had worn socks.
我觉得这段子挺给力的
I thought it was pretty spicy.
尤其是亲吻她下面那只眼那段
Especially the part where he kisses her nether eye.
你要是知道那指什么
You might not like it as much
可能就不会很喜欢了
if you knew what "nether eye" meant.
提示  要是很注意卫生的人
Hint: if one cares about hygiene,
就不该去亲吻那个地方
one ought not be kissing it.
好了  到我了
Okay, my turn.
佩妮  真心话还是大冒险
Penny, truth or dare?
真心话
Truth.
你为什么还一直跟莱纳德在一起
Why are you still hanging out with Leonard so much
即便你们已经分手了
even though you broke up with him?
真是个好问题
Oh, that's an excellent question.
对于已经分手不是一对的两人
For two people who claim to be no longer pair-bonded,
你们俩在一起的时间出乎寻常地多
you spend an inordinate amount of time in each other's company.
是啊
Yeah.
我选大冒险
Dare.
规则肯定不会允许
I don't believe the rules allow
你临时更改选择的
for an ex post facto option change.
是啊
Yeah.
我们只是不再是男女朋友
Okay, look, just because we're not seeing each other anymore
并不意味着不再是朋友
doesn't meanwe can't be friends.
毕竟莱纳德是个好人
I mean, Leonard's a great guy.
那你为什么要跟他分手
Then, why did you terminate your relationship with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
他太认真了  而我还没准备好
He got really serious, and I wasn't ready for it.
有意思
Interesting.
那如果以后
How will you react if, in the future,
你准备好了  而莱纳德已另结新欢
you become ready for it, and Leonard is unavailable,
因为另外有个女人意识到
because another woman has realized that he is--
用你的话说"他是个好人"  那你怎么办
to use your words--"a great guy"?
你只能问一个问题
You can only ask one question.
那问后面一个
That one.
我不想玩这个游戏了
You know what,  I don't want to play anymore.
不知道这游戏怎么算得分
Well, I'm not sure how this is scored,
但相信我们俩赢了这局
but I believe we may have won.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
你去哪了
Where did he go?
我们在找谢尔顿  不是马默杜克[大丹麦狗]
We're looking for Sheldon,not Marmaduke.
你刚吹口哨了?
You whistled?
这是什么
What is that?
《法柜奇兵》的胶片
Raiders of the Lost Ark
带那加长的21秒的
with 21 additional seconds.
我看不到  别人也休想看到
If I can't see it, no one else can see it.
谢尔顿  你疯了
Sheldon, this is crazy.
不  放映室没人看管那才叫疯了
No. Crazy was leaving the projection booth unattended.
听我说
Listen to me.
你累过头了  没法正确思考
You are over-tired. You're not thinking right.
趁麻烦还没惹大  赶紧放回去
Put the movie back before we get into trouble.
麻烦就是我的中间名  莱纳德
Trouble is my middle name,Leonard.
其实是李  但我喜欢用"麻烦"
Actually, it's Lee,but I prefer Trouble.
看看他们放谁进来了
Oh, look who they let in.
别担心  威尔·惠顿  我正准备走
Don't worry, Wil Wheaton. I was just leaving.
[哼着《夺宝奇兵》里的插曲退场]
跟上  肖特·郎德
Come on, Short Round.
好
Yeah.
快  加油  快点
Come on, guys! Hurry up! Hurry up!
你腿上绑个尿袋跑跑试试
Let's see you run with a bag of urines trapped to your leg.
模仿电影《斑点》里的场景
科洛尼奥电影院是每年纪念《斑点》拍摄的地方
他拿走了影片  追上他
He's got the movie! Get him!
为什么需要的时候飞行艇永不出现
Why is there never a pontoon plane when you need one?
她进去很久了
She's been in there a long time.
明显  真心话大冒险玩输了她很伤心
Clearly, losing Truth or Dare upset her.
也许我们该转移下她的注意力
Perhaps we should try to take her mind off it
找个其他流行的睡衣派对游戏玩
with anothor popular slumber party activity.
-比如呢  -网上建议
- Ooh, like what? - Well, the Internet suggests
睡衣派对时  还经常可以做一些
that slumber party guests often engage
无害的女同试验
in harmless experimentation with lesbianism.
你到底看的是什么网站
Where exactly on the Internet have you been looking?
-佩妮  -艾米  什么事
- Penny?  - Oh, hey, Amy.
抱歉我这么心烦意乱  我只是...
Look, I'm sorry I got so upset. I just...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
别担心  我会避开下面那只眼的
Don't worry. I'll avoid the nether eye.
我宁愿选择玩吃生曲奇饼的
I might have gone with eating raw cookie dough.